

# RODRIGUEZ **LÉANE** Étudiante

- 29 rue des greniers à grains #67350 Ettendorf # France
- ☑ leane.roz@gmail.com
- **&** (+53) 551 218 66

#### SOCIAL

- @LéaneRodriguez
- **梦** @FrankSiret

#### PROFILE

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science & Full Stack Developer. With good skills in mathematics, algorithms, and programming languages. I have several years of experience and achievements in the labor field. I like to improve my skills and I always push myself the most.

## EDUCATION

#### COMPUTER SCIECE

Universidad de Oriente - Cuba 2014 - 2019

- Graduated with Gold Title and Scientific Merit Award.
- Second best students from the 2019 class.
- Several scientific events related to Computer Science.
- Involved for 5 years in the ICPC Competitive Programming.
- Degree Thesis in the field of Information Retrieval.

#### EXPERIENCE

## Software Developer

From 2021 | People Walking 🥝

- Designed and developed UI/UX application for the Clinic University of Navarra (CUNATIC).
- Developed the API Backend for CUNATIC application using **Spring Boot** framework from scratch.
- Automate software development, such as build, test, and deployment, following continuous integration and continuous delivery guidelines using **Jenkins**.
- Get started as a junior developer in Android/IOS app development using **Flutter** technology.
- Designed and developed UI/UX for a centralized backup center application for Ancert.
- Support junior developer boot camps on React JS and helped improve their knowledge in the library.
- Developed reusable components that help the team to finish Backup Center project earlier than planned.
- Fully remote work, completing assigned tasks on time, meeting customer requirements and working under pressure.
- Daily work progress reports following the workflow set by the team using Beanstalk source version control software and Jira software development Tool.

Technologies used

React JS Typescript Bootstrap 4 Ant Design

Spring Boot (with JHipster) PostgreSQL

## Computer Science Professor

From 2019 | Universidad de Oriente

- Teaches classes of Logic Math, Data Structures, Information Retrieval System, and Artificial Inteligence.
- Stands as Director of the International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) at the University.
- Won the annual CITMA Award for Young Researchers.

#### Freelance Full-Stack Developer

From 2020 to 2021 | Freelance

- Designed and developed websites for small business.
- Guided digital marketing strategy for positioning the business on the web.
- Developed frontend user interface.
- Worked in a team of two members using agile methodologies (XP).
- Conducted meetings with the client and designed application architecture.

Technologies used

React Bootstrap 4 API Platform Swagger MySQL

#### C++ Developer

From 2017 to 2021 | Centro de Biofísica Médica

 Contributed to designed and developed the medical imaging software Imagis.

Company to many alastral and a second of the second balance that is the soul and also

## SKILLS

- Html / Sss
- Sass
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Spring Boot
- Flutter
- C/C++
- Java

- Support junior developer on C++ and neiped improve their knowledge in the language.
- Worked in more than 10 features such as design, report management, transmission, visualization, and image segmentation.

Technologies used

C++ Java VTK ITK DCMTK Qt Framework Lucene
Information Retrieval

## CERTIFICATES

#### **React Certificate**

Dec 2020 | HackerRank

Provide knowledge and skills required to become a successful web and mobile application developer.

## **Problem Solving Certificate**

Nov 2020 | HackerRank

Standardized assessment to help developers prove their coding skills.

#### LANGUAGES

• Spanish • English

## INTERESTS

